MARIA AMÉLIA NADIA BUESCHLEN

Sandmatten 14 ♦ Meiringen, Bern, 3860 ♦ +41 79 698 59 86 ♦ maria-bueschlen@outlook.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a motivated and adaptable person with concluded work experience which will utilize the organization and communication skills developed through my job in a Tourism organization. My strength is in reliability, punctuality and working well under pressure. I work well independently or with others as a team.

SKILLS

Reliable Team Player Accustomed to shift work Active Listening Skill Fast and efficient service worker Organized multi-tasker Ouick learner

WORK HISTORY

Customer Service Representative / Financial Assistant, 08/2013 to 08/2016 Mountain Railway Company Meiringen-Hasliberg, Twing

- Promptly and empathetically handled guest concerns and complaints.
- Strictly followed all cash, security, inventory and labor policies.
- Performed all position responsibilities accurately and in a timely manner.
- Consistently provided friendly guest service and heartfelt hospitality.

Bartender, 05/2016 to 10/2016

Trend Business AG Princess Club, Lucerne and

Waitress, 08/2016 to 10/2016

Ballenberg Swiss Culture Open-Air Museum, Brienzwiler

- Greeted customers and provided excellent customer service.
- Reported to all shifts wearing a neat, clean and unwrinkled uniform.
- Verified that prepared food met all standards for quality and quantity.
- Demonstrated integrity and honesty while interacting with guests, team members and managers

Baker / Customer Service Representative, 01/2017 to 07/2017 Nesters Market. North Vancouver

- Maintained clean and safe environment in the kitchen.
- Cooked and packaged large batches of food that was prepared to order.
- Prepared a variety of foods according to customer's orders or supervisor's instructions.
- Followed food safety procedures according to company policies, health and sanitation regulations.

Secretary / Financial Assistant / Customer Service Representative, 12/2017 to 04/2018 Bellwald Snowsportschool, Wallis

- Maintained high standards of customer service during high-volume, fast-paced operations.
- Prepare, key in, edit and proofread correspondence, invoices, presentations, brochures, publications, reports and related material from machine dictation and handwritten copy
- Answer telephone and electronic enquiries and relay telephone calls and messages
- Compile data, Payroll programme, also with data entry, statistics, and other information to support research activities

Present job, Receptionist, 05/2018 - present

Das Hotel Panorama, Hasliberg Reuti

Community Service

Volleyball Club VBC Brienz-Meiringen Soccer Club SV Meiringen

> I Support my teams with helping at special events

Computer skills

I have participated courses in Office Uses: Abacus, MS Word, Excel, Power Point and Skidata

EDUCATION

Business/Tourism Diploma:

Business woman/Tourism, Bildungszentrum BZI, Interlaken

Service Excellence Diploma:

Business/Customer service, ILAC International Language College, Vancouver

AFFILIATIONS

- blood donation member
- emergency aid certificate

CERTIFICATIONS

- Swiss business/German certificate
- English Cambridge certificates
- Azurlingua certificate in French
- IELTS certificate